莫格累了
Mog was tired.
她快累死了
She was dead tired.
她的头 转不动了
Her head was dead tired.
她的爪子没力了
Her paws were dead tired.
就连她的尾巴 也没有力气了
Even her tail was dead tired.
莫格心想“我要睡到天荒地老"
Mog thought "I wanna sleep forever."
于是 她睡了
And so she did.
这对你 是不是太低龄了
Isn't this a bit young for you?
他偶尔还是喜欢看
Sometimes he still likes it.
我偶尔还是喜欢看
Sometimes I still like it.
你还好吗  孩子
Are you all right, son?
你爸挺正常的  你知道吗
Your dad was okay, you know?
我知道   -他挺正常
-Yeah. -He was okay.
我知道
Yeah.
凯莉
Kerry!
凯莉  可以帮我找本书吗  有动作场面的
Kerry, can you get me a book, something with some action.
什么事
What?
注意安全
Careful now.
说吧
Talk to me.
格丽
Gerri!
你在哪儿  格丽
Where are you, Gerri?
刚才的骰子 扔得很好了
Wow. That's actually a perfect roll.
去吧  格丽
Yeah, Gerri,
去帮我们挡子弹吧  谢了  朋友
you jump on that grenade for us. Thanks, pal.
不行  感觉不对  我不想要田纳西大道
No. It doesn't seem right. I don't want Tennessee Avenue.
那轮到我了
My turn, then.
让我中吧
And if we call it.
我又一次 踩到你的破地盘了
-And once again I'm on the shit.
上交给我吧
That'll be me.
一百五
One-fifty.
我知道 你想让老爸 做什么
You know, I know what you tried to do with Dad.
什么意思  我以为
What? I thought that
这不是你梦寐以求的吗 哥
would've kinda been your dream, Rome.
我用你的老二 干翻格丽
Me fucking Gerri with your dick.
赶紧的  屌照男  付钱吧
Come on, dick pickler. Pay up.
七步  完美啊
Seven, hey, that was perfect.
看啊  是逃离监狱卡
Hey. Get-out-of-jail-free card.
又一个
-Another one.
你想卖掉吗
-You wanna sell that?
服务员来了  不错
Oh, waitress service. Okay.
请给我来一杯自由古巴 和总汇三明治 谢谢
I shall have a Cuba Libre and a club sandwich, please.
好的  让我去拿一些儿童菜单
Oh, okay. Well, let me grab a couple of kid's menus
立马回来
and I'll be right back.
好的
Okay.
这里的服务 又怪又慢
The service here is weird and slow
甚至会跟我老爸上床
and fucking my dad.
你还想玩吗  小威
-Okay... -You still into this, Will?
你想去花园里转转吗
You wanna take a turn around the gardens?
不用  挺好的
No, I'm good.
拜托了  威拉  嫁给他吧
Oh, come on, Willa, marry him.
他可能也只剩下十年寿命
He's probably got, like, 10 years left in him
之后你就能 享受天伦之乐了
and then it's all gravy.
我不希望我的私人事务
I do not wish my private affairs
成为茶余饭后的谈资  好吗
to become the subject of table chat, okay?
好  我得走了  我可以把我的财产转移给小西吗
Okay, I have to go. Can I give my properties to Shiv?
不 不行   -不行 不行
-No... No... No...
为什么  你必须拍卖掉他们  你他妈要去哪儿
-Why?  You have to auction them, where the fuck are you going?
接受无聊的福布斯访谈
Okay, the silly Forbes profile piece.
我把泛美市民台 变成了一台印钞机
I'm turning ATN Citizens into a cash machine
他们想知道 我怎么办到的
and they wanna know how I did it.
挑起最大限度的跟风热度  不就成了
Well, by turning on the bigot spigot to full gush.
说是“跟风热度”有点偏颇和无理了
Well, "bigot spigot" is a little reductive and unfair
但  不管怎样  回头见
but, anyway, goodbye.
再见  汤姆   -再见
-Bye, Tom. -Bye-bye.
小西.  -记得提到我
-Shiv. -Talk about me.
我会的
Will do.
小西  -怎么了
-Shiv. -What?
我觉得 你好像不小心作弊了
I think you might have accidentally been cheating?
有吗  我偷钱只是为了赢
What? I was only stealing so I could win.
是啊  作是游戏的一部分
-Yeah, cheating's part of it. -Oh, look at you
听着... 小西  你真的认为
Shiv, do you think that
好人会盗窃吗
stealing is what good people do?
盗窃啊  玩大富翁还作弊
Stealing, cheating at Monopoly, come on.
对吧   -拜托
Come on.
好  他来了  对他好点
Okay, well, he's here. Be nice.
好  我会对浮排上的科特·柯本友善点  [温馨乐队主唱27 岁自杀]
Yes, I will be nice to Kurt Cobain of the fucking floaties.
你好  -你好啊
-Hi. -Hey.
他要过来了
He's just coming.
他需要点时间
He needs a minute.
我们... 很感激你做的事
We appreciate what you did.
没什么的
It was nothing.
当然
Sure.
但是  你知道吗
But, hey, you know
如果下次 你再发现他在泳池里
if you find him in the pool again
然后 放任他溺死 的话
there's a C-note in it for you
我就给你一百块  好吗
to just let him sink, okay?
玩笑开得太早了
"Too soon," said the room.
他基本没事了  医院让他住一晚上.
He's basically fine, they just kept him overnight to...
说实话  我也不知道为什么
I don't know why, actually,
因为我听不懂意大利语  但是...
because I don't speak Italian but
没有媒体发现
no media pick up,
所以  一切都好
so, all good.
很好
Good.
很好  很好
Good. Good.
天啊   -你好  伙计
-Jesus. -Hey, buddy.
你好  -肯尼
-Hey. -Kenny.
你好啊  你好吗
-Hey. -What's up, Ken?
你好   -你还好吗  兄弟
-Hey. -You okay, brother?
很好
All good.
咱...咱别载歌载舞地庆祝  好吗
Let's just not make a whole song and dance, okay?
我觉得  我们更要载歌载舞地庆祝了
Well, I think we will make a song and dance.
你差点死  肯
You nearly drowned, Ken.
不  他只是从充气床上掉下来
Oh. No, he just fell off an air-bed, he's fine.
他没事   -喝了太多柠檬甜酒而已
One too many limoncellos.
不用大惊小怪   -是吗
No biggie.  Yeah.
好  我要把孩子们带走了  我想
Okay. I'm just gonna grab my kids, I guess...
他们今晚可以在这儿过夜
They can stay here, I'm sure, tonight,
这样更方便的话
if it's easier.
我不会让孩子们和他待在一块儿   -那好吧
-I'm not leaving them with him. -All right, then.
那就 皇室婚礼时见了
I guess we'll see you at the royal wedding then.
或许吧
Maybe.
我可能要回家一趟
I might need to get home.
我要和新律师们谈谈
I'm talking to new lawyers.
新律师吗  全新的律师吗
New lawyers? Like new, new lawyers?
是的  我不能透露更多  但  是的
Yeah. Well, I can't really say but, yeah,
让你知道一下
just so you know, we're...
我们...我们在讨论把过去五年
Yeah, we're discussing, putting everything
所有相关文件 和我的通讯记录
like all the papers and all my communications
放在照片墙[Instagram]上
for the last five years up on my Insta.
放照片墙上吗
On, Insta?
肯
Ken.
对了  康福莉
And, Comfry
名利场可能会出一大篇幅报道  关于我的事
Vanity Fair might be doing a big thing with me
所有的事  所以...
the whole thing, so...
我不确定  总之我准备好了...
Yeah, I don't know, whatever. I'm ready to... I'm just...
我...我准备好投入其中了
I'm ready to really get into it all.
但是
But...
总之  谢了
yeah, thanks for...
谢谢  好了  孩子们  走吧
Thanks. Okay, kids, let's go.
赶紧走吧
Let's go.
他们要来了
They're coming.
好吧  老兄
All right, man.
待会儿见   -对
-Later. -Yeah.
他看起来正常吗
He seems good.
天啊
Oh, man.
我们与名利场...有在接触中
We have been talking to... Vanity Fair,
但...主要是我们在联系他们
but it's...It's mostly us calling them.
爸  你还好吗  一切都好吗
Hey. Dad, you good? We good?
需要我加入那通电话吗
Do you want me on that call?
不用   -好的
-No. -Okay.
继续  卡尔  什么事
Go on, Karl, what?
司法部可能要 制裁我们一笔 史无前例的罚款
DOJ is gonna likely hit us with a historic fine.
GoJo的市值已经超过我们的了
GoJo's market cap has overtaken ours.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  但...那早已发生了 所以...
Okay, yeah, but that... That was already happening, so.
GoJo 的董事会可能会考虑其他的选择
GoJo's board may be considering entertaining other options.
什...什么   -是的
-What? -Yeah.
搞什么鬼  好吧  那他要停止交易吗
What the fuck? Okay, well, is he gonna pull the plug?
还是 GoJo 小罗   你知道这回事吗
Or is GoJo... Rome, do you know?
合并 他忍了
He swallowed the merger
但我不确定 他还能再忍多少要求
but I don't know how much more he can fucking eat.
好  别着急担心
Oh, okay, don't get all sweaty, Betty.
我会去搞清楚  然后发你邮件  好吗
I'm gonna figure it out and I'll drop you an email, okay?
谢了  -我要见马特森
-Thanks. -I'm gonna see Matsson.
理清内情
Get inside this!
要我跟你一起去吗  爸
Do you want me to come with you, Dad?
不用  待在这儿  玩你的老二吧
No. Stay here and play with your dick.
我可以跟你去  爸
I can come with you, Dad...
这并不麻烦...   -不 不
-It's not an... -No...
不  我开玩笑的  说笑呢
I'm kidding.
来吧  小兔崽子
No, come on, Tumbledown.
他是你朋友
He's your pal.
咱们去见见这位安徒生崽子
Let's go see Hans Christian Anderfuck
看他是不是 一直在给我们讲童话故事
and see if he's been telling us fucking fairy tales.
继   承   之   战
第 3 季  第 9 集
本季终
你还好吗
You okay?
漂亮女人  不是吗
Good-looking woman, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
当然
Yup.
你是怎么回事  儿子
So what is it, son?
你怕女人的性器官吗
Are you scared of pussy?
还是你满脑子 都是搞基画面
Is it all screens or up the ass with you or what?
天哪  当然不是  老爸  能不能不...
Jesus, no, God. Dad, can we not...
那
That's...
这.. 我只是恶搞一下  没别的
That was just being horrible,
我挺好的   -是啊  操逼罢了
it's good, it's all good. Yeah. Well, it's just fucking...
如果你需要变直
If you need to get straightened out
就赶紧去
-get straightened out.
明白吗  明白
Okay? -Yeah.
其他我不需要知道
I don't wanna know.
欢迎
-Welcome. -Hey.
很荣幸  终于和你见面了  先生
So nice to finally meet you in person, sir.
彼此彼此
Likewise.
感谢莅临
Thank you for coming.
客气了
Not at all.
跟我说说你的想法
So, what do you think?
我们是要合并  还是算逑了
Are we doing this fucking merger or not?
真是开门见山
Wow. Just straight in there, huh?
你知道  我年纪大了
Oh, yeah, well, you know, I'm old.
难道还要我寒暄
What do you want, a bit of a,
哦 好漂亮的房子啊
"Oh, what a nice house you got here"?
不是的  我喜欢  我很容易觉得无聊
No, I... I like it. I get bored easily.
世间万物皆无聊  不是吗
Yeah, everything is boring, isn't it?
是啊  世间万物无聊透顶
Yeah, everything is pretty fucking boring.
除了这个
Except this.
的确  你勾起了我的兴趣    -有多感兴趣
-Yeah, you got me interested. -How interested?
听着  我不想一直兜圈子
Look, I don't wanna fuck around forever with this.
我看过你的市值
I mean, I've seen how your price is
我知道你的董事会 在寻觅其他买家
and I understand that your board is looking at all the options
但是  如果我们密切合作
but if we stay tight,
这生意就能成
this can work.
所以.
So...
我们是接着闲聊  还是
shall we dance or what?
要坐下来聊吗   -好啊
-Do you wanna sit down? Yeah. -Sure.
扎克伯格曾经
Zuckerberg wants...
对了  你认识他吗
Do you know Mark, by the way?
他曾跟我说
Well, he once told me that...
古罗马时期有段时间
in ancient Rome, at one point,
奴隶主想让奴隶穿特定的衣服
they wanted to make all the slaves wear something
以便确认身份
so they could identify them.
在上面
It's just up here.
比如...那叫什么来着
Like... what do you call these things?
像斗篷一样的
Like a cloak or whatever.
后来  他们打消了这个念头
But then they decided not to do it
你知道其中原因吗   -说说看
and you know why?  -Hmm？
因为奴隶主们意识到  如果所有的奴隶穿着一致
Because they realize if all the slaves dressed the same
他们就会知道 自己人数众多
they would see how many of them there were
他们会起义  反抗  杀死奴隶主
and they'd rise up and kill their masters.
我们不喜欢马克
Yeah, we don't love Mark.
那又如何  难道现在他有个马来西亚仆人
So what? Does he have some kid in Malaysia
在给他读历史故事吗
reading history for him now?
我不知道
I don't know.
我的意思是  如果我们要生存
But the point is if we wanna survive
你和我
you and I, then...
我们就需要一大堆 小人物
we need a hell of a lot of little folks
给我们提供数据
running around shitting us data
以此吸引眼球  提高利润  扩大规模
you know, for the eyeballs, for the revenue, for the scale.
无意冒犯  我认为你没有达这个目标的
No offense but I don't think you have the technology
技术和计划
or the orientation to get there.
而你没有内容
And you don't have the content.
或许吧  但是
Well, maybe not but
我们的业绩一飞冲天
we're flying like a fucking rocket ship
你们却是日落西山
and you're sinking like a lead balloon.
你的计划是什么
What's your churn like?
听说你们的观众流失严重
Yeah, we hear you have problems with binge and burn.
我们手上有好料
We got the good stuff.
那是当然  你们手上的内容挺吸引人  但是
Sure, sure, some of your content is pretty cool, I guess, but...
生意归生意  你们该扩大规模  或整体出售了
business-wise, it's time for you to beef up or sell out.
你们无法转型为科技公司
And you can't become a tech player
因为你和你的公司都太他妈老了
because you and your business are just too fucking old.
说话悠着点  他身体棒着呢  你知道和他在操谁吗
Whoa... He is in great shape. You know who he's fucking?
无意冒犯  因为你是个传说
I don't wanna be rude because you're a legend.
说实话  你基本上  刀枪不入
Honestly, you're fucking bulletproof.
就像坦克一样
Tank man.
你是要我  跟你一起去桑拿
So, you want me to come in your sauna
对你的老二 夸奖一番吗
and tell you what a pretty pecker you got?
我只是 很期待未来 而已
I'm just really excited about the future.
我也是
So am I.
你是
Yeah, but...
真心话吗
are you? Really?
这个嘛  正如你所言
Well...that's something you say, isn't it?
当然  我很期待
No, but I am excited.
但是..
But...
美国...
America...
我不知道
I don't know.
我初来乍到时  这里的豪门贵族
When I arrived, there were these gentle giants
空气里都是黄金和奶香味
smelling of fucking gold and milk
他们无所不能
they could do anything.
现在  看看他们
Now look at them,
要么脑满肠肥
fat as fuck,
要么像吸了毒  或练了瑜伽一样  骨瘦如柴
scrawny on meth or yoga.
数典忘祖
They pissed it all away.
我不知道发生了什么
I don't know.
我不知道
接着说下去
Go on. Talk to me.
我看咱们挺合适的
Well, I think we fit.
咱俩的公司挺搭的
Your company and mine.
但是  你知道
But, you know,
我们是华尔街的宠儿
the street loves us, we're...
我们非常抢手
We're a strong buy.
业绩蒸蒸日上  居高不下
We're up and we're staying there.
而你  你们...
And you, you have this...
有罚款要交  还有其他糟心事
this fine, and all this other bullshit.
伤痕累累
You're hurt
或者  心力憔悴
or maybe you're tired.
所以  应该是我来收购你
So, I make sense as the person to take over.
如果这个选项
Now, if that's an option
你可以考虑一下
if that's something you would consider,
那么我们接着谈
then let's talk.
但  如果你想叫我滚一边儿去
But if you wanna tell me to go fuck myself
那就明说
tell me to go fuck myself.
你不是开玩笑吧
You're not fucking serious.
我不会让你难堪
I would make everything nice for you.
我可以赔钱给你  或者你愿意的话
I could pay you out or if you want
赋予你公司一切事物的控制权
control inside or outside of the assets you love
没有问题
that's cool.
我会给足你面子
I would want you to maintain prestige.
绝不贬低你
I'm not about making you small.
但要听你发号施令
But you'd rule the roost
董事会就是你的了
it would be your board.
我会重新调整架构
But I would structure it
让你舒舒服服
so fucking nice for you.
我注意到  你并没有起身揍我
I notice you're not punching me on the nose.
爸   -没事的  儿子
Dad?  That's okay, son.
我不知道   -你在想什么
I don't know. -What are you thinking?
休想让我告诉你  我他妈在想什么
I'm not telling you what I'm fucking thinking.
我知道你他妈在想什么
Well, I know what you're fucking thinking.
你在想 自己全身上下的细胞都想让
You're thinking every bit of me wants to tell this
这片盐渍生蛙鱼[自嘲]
slab of gravlax
有多远 滚多远
to go fuck himself...
但还有一小部分  知道我说的句句在理
except for the bit that knows that every word he says is true.
我不知道  我不确定我能否接受
I don't know, I'm not sure I can swallow this.
如果是家族的问题  我能理解
If this is a family thing, I get it.
我能理解你的焦虑
I... I appreciate the anxiety.
至于你儿子
And in terms of your son
他会是此次整合的关键人物
he would be essential to the integration process.
绝非虚言
One hundred percent crucial.
关键先生  你们家族的门面
Key element. The face of the family.
至于你公司里的高管团队
As for the rest, your top team
我很乐意适才适用
I'd be happy to assess each according to their abilities.
不行
This is not happening.
好吧
Right.
不行
No.
行  我明白了
No. I see that. Understood.
问问也无妨
It was worth asking, huh?
听着  你想不想
But listen, do you wanna...
再逗留一会儿
do you wanna stick around for a bit?
看看能不能做成之前的交易
We can see if the old deal has a shape
其他小生意
side snacks, maybe.
你在以色列的人工智能项目
You have that Israeli AI operation
我也很感兴趣
I might be interested in.
资产交换之类的
An asset swap sort of thing?
有何不可 很好
Why not?  Cool.
罗曼  你该回去了
Roman, you better get back.
你妈明天大喜之日
You know your mom and all her brouhaha for tomorrow.
好的  当然了  当然
All right, yeah, sure thing, sure thing.
我可不想错过婚礼
Don't wanna miss the old nuptials.
你说真的吗  你想让我
Wait, but yeah? you want...
我妈明天要和一糟老头子再婚了
Well yeah You know, my mom is getting remarried to a bowl of porridge
可把我感动坏了  所以我可能要走了
and it's all terribly moving so I should probably...
但 还是要谢谢你
But thank you.
婚礼见  老爸
See you over there, Pop.
失陪一下
Excuse me for one second.
回来啦  怎么样  -回来了
-Hey! So? -Hey.
怎么样  大富翁玩到哪了
So? How was the Monopoly?
你抽到机会卡 交所得税了吗
Did you have to pay some income tax for the novelty value?
平等合并吗   -什么平等合并
Merger of equals.  Merger of equals?
这事还成不成啊  罗曼
Well, is it happening or not? Rome?
没人跟我说过 有可能会平等合并啊
I was not alerted to this merger of equals possibility.
马特森想要去除我这类人的平台作用
Matsson wants to de-platform guys like me.
把异见者 都收入他的数字集中营当中
Round up the Maverick thinkers into his digital gulag.
不好意思
If you don't mind
我被我们老大哥的事 搅得心烦意乱的
I'm a little bit churned up about my big brother
我现在 没法思考这些事情
so I can't really think about that shit right now.
不介意的话 等会说吧
Talk about it later.
你们好啊   -你好
-Hey. -Hi.
你们好  -你好
-Hello. -Hello.
你们这是要干嘛  -坐吧
-So, what is this? -Just take a seat.
过来
Come on.
行
Okay.
是这样
So...
我们就是想一起见个面
we just wanted to get together
告诉你  我们爱你
to let you know that we love you.
什么
-What? -
明白吗   -我真的爱你
Right? -I love you straight up.
我感觉.. 反正我不想你死  所以...
-I mean, I...suppose I don't want you to die, so,
就是这样
yeah.
这是怎么回事  你们什么招数
What is this? What's the angle?
没有什么招数
No angle.
我们很担心你
We're worried that you...
是不是有意无意地 试图要
consciously or subconsciously tried to...
你们是不是想 打压我
Are you trying to shut me down?
你差点就自杀成功了  兄弟
You kind of tried to kill yourself, dude
这可一点也不好玩
and that's not cool.
我是从充气垫上掉了下来   -行吧
-I fell off an inflatable. -Okay.
这是场心理干预吗
Is this an intervention?
你们有什么资格 给我做心理干预
Why do you get to do an intervention on me?
认真的吗
Seriously?
你需要心理干预
Well, you need an intervention.
你需要心理干预  你也需要心理干预
You need an intervention, you need an intervention.
是是是  你说得对
Yeah, totally, yeah, yeah
但是  现在  你才是最需要这个的人
but you're kind of the top of the pile right now
你们明天给我做吧  行吗
we'll do me tomorrow. Yeah?
是的  自杀  超过了可以接受的范围
Yeah, suicides jump the line.
我他妈就是从浮排上掉下去了而已   -你是个瘾君子
-I fell off my fucking floatie. -You're an addict.
你喝酒上瘾  吸毒上瘾
You're addicted to booze, and to drugs
你对恋爱 性 工作 还有家庭闹剧 都上瘾了
and relationships, and sex, and work, and the family drama.
不  抱歉  你说的不对  看看你们自己吧
No, sorry, no. I mean, look who's fucking here.
我看不出你说的那些问题
I don't see it.
你们有什么立场指控我
You don't have any standing
所以说  听着  你们几个  收一收
so listen, you guys can take this little committee
公共安全委员会的做派  快滚蛋吧
of public fucking safety and fuck off.
你必须停手  不要再试图杀死咱爸了
You need to stop trying to kill Pop.
明白吗  自私鬼
Okay? You're selfish
永远都只想着你自己   -康纳  你能不能
-you're self-centered. -Connor, can you just...
·干嘛   -就是
-What? -Just...
我难道不能 说我想说的话了吗
-I'm not allowed to say my piece?
不是  你当然可以说  但是   -不这是
-No, you can. Just...
我来领头  行吗
Let me lead, yeah?
行  听着
Okay look.
我听你们说的
I hear you.
但是  我觉得..
But I just... I... I feel
是这样..
like
我所做的一切...
everything I've done
本意都是好的
has been with good intentions
我是真的觉得 我做的所有事
and I... I do think this is actually
都是为了你们 和你们那些破事 而不是我
about all of you and your shit more than me.
虽然听起来 我好像
It sounds like I'm...
是在自我辩解  但 我没有
I'm being defensive when I'm not.
我说了  我会听你们的
I'm... I'm saying I'm hearing you.
是吗
Mm-hmm？
但是  你们能明白吗
But it's like, do you have any idea
那种感觉
how it feels
作为家里的长子
as the eldest son
得到了
to be,
某些许诺  然后一下子就
you know, promised something and then...
这样
you know,
没了希望  那是什么感觉  我懂
just have it taken?  Yeah.
是啊   -我才是长子
Sure, man. I'm the eldest son.
你说什么
What was that?
我才是长子
I am the eldest son.
没错  你当然是了  但是你知道他是什么意思  老康
Well, yeah, obviously, Con, but you know what he means.
我才是长子
I am the eldest son
你们他妈的  谁都没跟我提什么 平等合并 的事
and no one told me about this fucking merger of fucking equals.
要是我想接管公司呢
And what if I wanna take over
我才是真正的长子   -好了
because I am the eldest son? -All right.
冷静点  老康
-Easy. Easy, Con.
我们...知道了  我是长子  我是长子
-Let's... okay. Okay. -I'm the eldest son. I'm the eldest son.
考虑考虑我
And I must be considered
我也有话语权
and I need to be taken into account.
老康  我们在说的是
Con, we're... We're talking about...
我失去了什么   -闭嘴吧
-what I actually lost. -Shut up.
怎么  你觉得受伤了
What, you're hurt?
我有三年没见着老爸了
I didn't see Pop for three years
你还嫌弃你的金汤匙不够亮
but your spoon wasn't shiny enough?
是吗
Huh？
世界不是围着你转的
Well, it is not all about you.
我以为你爱我    -混蛋
I thought you loved me. Asshole,
我当然爱你  我爱你们三个蠢货
I do love you. I love all three of you pricks
但这换来了什么  你们剩下的那一点点残羹冷炙
but what do I get from you chumps but chump change.
微不足道的零头  去他妈的吧
fucking chump change.  Well, fuck you.
我到这来参加你们妈妈的婚礼  我刚跟我的未婚妻求婚
I'm here for your mom's wedding and I proposed to my fiancée
但你们
and no one
谁都没来祝贺我
has said congratulations.
一个都没有
No one.
不管怎么说
But I am
我才是老爸的大儿子
the eldest son of our father.
我才是
I am.
是我
Me.
是他  没错
He is him.
滚蛋
fuck off!
不是  是另一个
No, no, it's the other one.
就快来了  马上来接你
It's coming, it's coming for you.
你没事吧  老康  -当然没事
-You okay, Con? -Yeah, yeah.
我就是有点累了
Just a little tired.
抱歉  昨晚翻来覆去的动静
Sorry about the tossing and turning,
那个空调怎么都弄不好
I just couldn't get the AC right -you know?
空调啊   那确实
-The AC. Yeah.  Sure.
而且我的家人讨厌我
Plus, my family hates me.
我要把泛美 拱手让给一个 天杀的瑞典人了
I'm gonna lose ATN to a goddamn Swede
竞选没戏了  你就要离开我了
so my campaign is fucked, and you're gonna leave me.
可我 真的很爱你
And I love you.
就是这样
So, yeah.
那些事情加上空调  我真的累了
Yeah, that and the AC.
怎么还不来
Come on.
老康  -怎么了
Con? What?
你是个好人
You're a nice man.
好的  谢谢
Right. Thanks.
我想告诉你
You know what?
去他妈的
fuck it.
什么去他妈的   -去他妈的
-fuck it?  -fuck it.
你是说
As... As in?
去他妈的吧
fuck it!
别难过  再惨能惨到哪去呢  是不是
Come on. How bad can it be? Right?
真的吗   -对  何妨一试
-Really? -Yeah, why not?
我们会过得很快乐的
You know, we'll have fun.
有什么好计较的
fuck it,
是不是
right?
太对了
Hell yeah.
去他妈的吧
fuck it!
罗伊先生
Mr. Roy?
你的车到了
It's your car.
不管了  去他妈的
-fuck it, huh? -fuck it!
全都去他妈的
fuck it forever!
去他妈的
fuck it!
你好  -你好吗 卡尔
-Hi. -Hi, Karl. How you doing?
WiFi 怎么样
How's the Wi-Fi?
我献祭了几只羊  看上去好像管用了
I sacrificed a few goats so it seems to be working.
太棒了  托斯卡纳乡村地区  真正的商业中心
Great. Rural Tuscany's a real business hub.
他的精神怎么样
How are his spirits?
比如说  血糖情况怎么样
Like his... How's his blood sugar?
没问题  他一如既往神气十足
Yeah. He's amazing, as always.
那当然了 他是个铁人  真是了不起
Oh, yeah, of course. Powerhouse. Remarkable.
你见到爸了吗
Have you seen Dad?
怎么   -他会来吗
Hmm ? Is he coming?
爸会来吗  罗曼  你知不知道
Is Dad coming, Rome? -Do you know?
交易谈好了吗  好了  一切都会公之于众
Is the deal good? -Yeah. All will be revealed.
一切都会公之于众
All will be revealed.
这是什么意思啊
The fuck does that mean?
谁把你变得 也会打马虎眼了
Who made you the Wizard of fuck?
你什么都不知道  是不是
You don't know jack shit, do you?
你不想最后再跟妈 确认一下吗
Do you not think, one last check with Mom?
罗曼  我们就要进去了
Rome, we're about to go in.
好吧  我就是... 不知道他有没有得什么病
Right. It's just, I don't know if he's, you know.
你好啊 彼得   -你好
-Hey, Peter. -Hi.
谢谢   -祝你好运
Yeah. Good luck.
你担心妈妈看错了人吗
-You're not sure if he's the one?
我是担心婚前协议签没签 好吗
I'm worried about the prenup, okay?
她有婚前协议
She has a prenup.
她有对   -真的吗
-She had her... Yes! -She has...
她叫她的律师看过了
She had her lawyer look at it
因为 她想留着 爸给她的伦敦公寓
because she wants to keep the... the London flat that Dad gave her.
好吧  那如果他给她下毒呢
What if he poisons her?
如果他为了得到 超级想要的公寓
What if he pushes her down the stairs
要把她推下楼梯呢
to get this flat he so desires?
对啊  那如果更糟呢
Oh, yeah. And what if, worse,
他用鸡巴干她
he fucks her with his dick?
干得太爽  以致死亡呢
-fucks her so good that she dies?
你们好吗  孩子们
-How you doing, children?
你好 汤姆   你好 格雷格
-Oh, Tom. -Hey, Greg.
你介意和康福莉聊一下吗
Do you mind chatting with Comfry?
我想跟公主聊聊
I wanna check in on the princess.
现在叫她“公主"了吗  我以为她是女爵呢
The princess, now? I thought she was a Contessa?
对  但我猜  通过她的爸爸
Yeah, but I guess through her dad
她大概是 卢森堡的第八位 王位继承人
she's like, eighth in line for the throne of Luxembourg?
第八位继承人吗
Eighth in line?
格雷格  你要是娶了她  那么距离成为欧洲最奇怪的国王
Greg, you marry her you're a plane crash away
就差一场飞机失事了
from becoming Europe's weirdest king!
别逗了
-Don't be silly.
哥们  你杀掉几个血友病患者
-Dude you off a couple of hemophiliacs
就能成为卢森堡国王了
and you'll be the kind of Luxembourg.
然后 就能听着 像款豪华饼干
You'd sound like a fancy cookie.
其实是叫 大公爵
It's actually a Grand Duchy.
这和维也纳国会也有关系
It's something to do with the Congress of Vienna?
我猜这很复杂
It's, I guess, really complicated
她不喜欢聊这些
she doesn't like to talk about it
虽然 关于这个 我们确实聊了一些
although we do talk about it quite a bit.
看到了吗  现在
Oh. See, now?
是罗曼 去吧 格雷格
Roman. Get in there, Greg.
如果罗曼娶了她  他会侵略法国的
If Roman marries her he'll invade France.
等一下
Hold on.
是的 是
Yeah.
我会代你表示遗憾的
I'll send your regrets.
凯莉  我不会在那边吃饭
Kerry, I won't eat down there.
我回来后 会在我的房间吃蛋卷
I will take my omelet in my room, on my return.
没问题  我会告诉他们   -谢谢你
-Of course. I'll let them know. -Thank you.
抱歉 抱歉
Sorry. Sorry.
我没耽误事儿吧
I didn't delay things, did I?
别担心  肯德尔
No worries, Kendall.
我们还差几个人没到
We're just missing a couple of people, actually.
他没来
-He didn't come.
你不知道哪里.... 抱歉
-You don't know where...Sorry
你不知道哪里
You don't know where...
彼得  你最好还是面对吧
Peter I think you better face it that Logan is not gonna make it.
洛根不会来了
Logan's not coming
你可能得跟我结婚了  抱歉
You might have to just make do with me, sorry.
怎么样
-How about that?
亲爱的
-Darling.
你能忍受吗   -当然
-Can you bear it? -Of course.
话说   -嗯
Hey.  Hmm
罗曼   -干嘛
Rome. -Yeah?
我有个主意   -什么
-I have an idea.  Mm-hmm
他们过来的时候  你应该告诉妈妈  你爱她
When they come past, you should tell Mom you love her.
好  滚吧
Yeah, fuck off.
不  那样多浪漫啊
No, how romantic would it be,
想象一下  如果你能娶了妈妈
imagine that if you could marry Mommy
在她婚礼的日子   -对 对
on her wedding day?  Yeah.
或者 告诉他们一个 不能结婚的原因
Or tell them a reason that they can't be married.
因为她是唯一
Because she's the only one
能让她儿子的鸡鸡膨胀的人
who makes her son's pee-pee go boom boom.
欢迎 家人 朋友 和亲人们
Welcome, family, friends, and loved ones.
我们今天相聚于此
We are gathered here today in the face of this company
来参加彼得·蒂莫西·蒙加穆尼昂
for the wedding of Peter Timothy Munga Munion
和卡洛琳·亚历山德拉·海伦娜·圣约翰·科林伍德的婚礼
and Caroline Alexandra Helena St. John Collingwood.
她真的感动了  对吧
She's really feeling it, huh?
我喜欢婚礼   -我也是
-I love weddings. -Me, too.
对彼此做出 正式的承诺...
...they make to one another today.
我的天  她嗑了什么啊   -就是说
-Jesus, what is she on? Yeah.
快他妈的 把我杀了吧
Fucking kill me now.
好吧  大家好
Okay. Hi.
我妈 叫...
My mom has...
叫我说几句话
has asked me to say a few words
就几句
just this second.
首先出现在我脑海里的词 是
And the first words that came to mind were
糟糕  不  什么  婊子
"Shit, no, What? Bitch."
还有
And...
还有一些词  比如  那好吧   毫无准备
other words like "totally" and "unprepared."
好吧  那关于我妈  我能说些什么呢
Right. So what can I say about my mom?
她是我生命中的永恒
Well, she's been a constant in my life.
永恒的痛苦...
Constant pain in the...
但  我还是爱她
But I love her anyway,
我想这也证明了
which I guess is testament to
她是一个 多么引人瞩目的...
what a remarkable and...
复杂 又有趣的人
complicated and interesting person that she is.
我毫不怀疑  彼得  你在和她短暂的婚姻里
And I have no doubt, Peter, that you will never be bored
绝不会感到无聊
in the brief time that you're married. That's...
不过说真的  没人像我妈妈
But in all seriousness, there's no one like my mom.
你是个幸运的人
And you're a lucky guy.
我对你和她要共度的时光  感到嫉妒
And I am jealous of the time that you get to spend with her.
我希望你们的婚姻
I hope that your marriage is
会像我的一样  富有  快乐  有益  充实
as rich and happy rewarding, and fulfilling as mine.
那么  敬新娘和新郎
So here's to the bride and groom.
敬新娘和新郎   -敬新娘和新郎
The bride and groom!  To the bride and groom.
你觉得
Do you think...
你觉得  她是不是知道什么
Do you think she knows something?
我是说
I mean,
如果一切都崩盘了 怎么办
what if it's all fallen apart?
对吗  爸回来了
Yeah? Dad's back
那他为什么没出现   -放松点
-so why isn't he here? -Oh, relax.
这酷毙了
It's cool beans.
酷毙了?
Cool beans?
你什么时候开始说“酷毙”了
Since when do you say "cool beans"?
你他妈什么都不知道吧
You don't have a fucking clue, do you?
你们好
-Hey... -Hey.
你好   -你好
-Hi. -Hey.
听着  我觉得我们应该
Listen, I think we should
向你道歉  因为  不  没关...
say sorry for...No, doesn't matter,
没关系
doesn't matter.
忘了这件事吧   -已经忘了
Forget about it.  Forgotten.
那么
-Okay. -Yeah.
猜猜 是谁要迎娶
So guess who's gonna get married
世界上最好的姑娘了
to the greatest gal in the world?
不是吧  -她同意了吗
-No... -Oh. She said yes?
你终于搞定她了
Wow, you finally ground her down, huh?
恭喜你啊
Congrats, man.
对了  还有  威拉有跟凯莉聊过
Yeah. And, also, Willa's been talking to Kerry?
她知道爸在哪吗
Yeah. She know where Dad is?
她在装腔作势  但你们知道这是什么吗
She's sandbagging. But, do you know what this is?
那是历史上  另一个伟人的
That is another dried penis
干枯的阴茎  对吗
from one of the great men of history, correct?
不  秘鲁人参根
No. Maca root.
用在爸的奶昔里
For Dad's smoothie.
为什么凯莉在装腔作势
Why is Kerry sandbagging?
他在给宝宝糊糊加养料
He's working on his baby batter.
什么玩意儿啊  秘鲁人参根  杏仁酱
What's that? Maca root. Almond butter.
爸在做更有黏性 更强的粘稠物
Dad's putting together a more adhesive and potent gloop.
为了他的...
Working on his fucking...
他的精液  你是说...   -对
His jism? Are you...  -Yes.
你他妈跟我开玩笑呢  没有
-Are you fucking with me right now? No.
什么  -看他嚼了多少核桃
-What? -Look at all the walnuts he's been munching.
他会像鲶鱼一样甩出精子
He's gonna be rocking sperms like a little catfish.
我的天啊
Oh, my fuck.
爸在召集战士   -对
Dad's scrambling the fighters? -Yeah.
用秘鲁人参根  -别  滚开 拜托
And Maca root. -No. -fucking... come on.
不太好啊  不  除非你启动攻城引擎
-Not good.  No, you don't tangle with the root
你就别缠着这个根
unless you're firing up the siege engines.
我的天
Jesus.
我觉得恶心  -你们呢
I feel ill.  Do you?
我猜  他真的不看好你们吧
I guess he really doesn't rate you guys, huh?
谢谢   -不管怎样
-Thanks.  -Anyway,
觉得应该告诉你们   -谢谢你  非常感谢
thought I'd tell ya.   Thank you. Appreciate it.
好吧  那我们需要一个杀掉婴儿的计划
Okay. Well, we need a plan to kill this baby.
对
Yeah.
你终于 找到了一个 值得的对手
Wow. Finally, you found a worthy adversary.
发生什么了
Hey. What's going on?
没什么
Nothing.
只是爸在启动投石机
Just Dad cranking up the trebuchet you know...
什么  -试着生孩子
-What?  -Trying for a baby.
什么
-What?
可能他现在就在做呢
Maybe that's what he's doing right now.
对  可能
Yeah. Maybe
他正在产卵室里
he's in the spawn chamber
散播他的地狱种子  我能看得到
issuing his hellseed. Sure. I could see it.
那  可能我们也应该开始了吧  太空竞赛
Well, maybe we should get cracking? Space race?
什么  你们俩吗
What? You two?
我们应该说吗   -不不不
-Should we say? -No...
我知道的  其实..   -宝贝  别
-I know for a fact... -Babe, stop.
她不能怀孕  因为如果她可以的话
that she cannot get pregnant. Because if she could,
她早都...早都怀上了
she would have...  That would've happened by now.
她和很多男人做过
She has had a lot of sex with a lot of men.
我们可能会冻卵
We may be freezing.
你们会冻卵   -对
-Oh, you may be freezing? -Yeah.
好吧  好的
Oh, okay. Yeah.
你知道她 为什么让你 一直等着吧
You know why she's making you wait, right?
她是想让你来生孩子
She's gonna make you carry it.
真幽默   -是啊
-Very funny. -Yeah.
你得亲自把孩子“拉" 出来
You're gonna have to poop out your own baby
然后挤自己的小奶头
and then squeeze your little Tommy tits
搞点父乳出来
for man milk.
都在呢  -好吧 非常感谢
-Okay. -Thank you for...
我听说 拉里·范西塔特的私人飞机
I just heard that Larry Vansitart's PJ
刚刚降落在拉丹特
landed at La Dante
而他正前往 马焦雷湖[意大利北部]
and that he's headed to Lake Maggiore.
什么   -没错
-What? -Yeah.
拉里·范西塔特
Larry Vansitart?
和马特森一起吗  那意味着他要拉投资
With Matsson? That means financing.
为什么马特森
Why would Matsson...
是啊  为什么马特森要为全股票交易拉资金呢
Yeah. Why would Matsson need financing for an all-stock deal?
我正在努力了解
I'm trying to get a fix.
一直有几个助理在联系格雷格
And Greg has been contacted by some assistants.
格雷格   -没错
-Greg has? -Greg.
那我们先分头行动  再汇总信息吧
Yeah. So let's split up and pool, okay?
好的  -小罗
-Okay. All right. -Rome.
干吗    -你应该在内部密切关注这事的
-Yeah. -You're supposed to be inside track on this.
有很多可能性  我认为没什么大问题
That could be any number of things. I think it's fine.
我得去找凯莉  你能去找玛西娅说吗
I'm gonna hit Kerry, could you, talk to Marcia, maybe?
当然 可以  我会去爬爬
-Yeah. Sure. -Yeah? I'll scale
北面的艾格峰
the north face of the fucking Eiger.
真是操
Jesus fuck.
我试看给环保慈善机构
I mean, I guess I tried to feel better
捐很多钱
by giving a lot of money
来让自己好受些   是吗
to environmental charities. Oh, yeah?
哪一个...  还是说...
Which... or, like, to...
不是捐给了“绿色和平"吧
Not Greenpeace?
不是“地球之友"
No. Friends of the Earth.
好吧  那个慈善机构也不错
Okay. Oh, yeah, that's a good one.
不  我..
No, I...
我和“绿色和平“组织有些梁子
I have some beef with Greenpeace.
说来话长了  但他们很坏
Long story, but they're bad.
一个格陵兰岛的成员  一直领支票
Yeah. One guy in Greenland just cashing checks
吃企鹅
and eating penguins
还在冰川上用脚踩灭烟头
and stomping cigarettes out on glaciers.
那什么  你可以随意  无视他
Feel free to cut him down dead, by the way.
实际上  我们聊得挺愉快
We are actually having an interesting talk.
是啊  我想也是
Yeah. I'm sure you are.
在我们那儿  他被叫作无人在意的乞丐
He's what's called in our land an irrelevant pauper
你不需要听乞丐说话
and you don't need to listen to the pauper.
免得污了你们皇室的耳朵
It's not for your royal ears.
不不 不是的   -不是的
No. No-de-no. -No-de-no?
不是的  我的朋友
-No-de-no, my friend.
众所周知  他是...  -众所周知我什么
He's widely known... -I'm widely known?
你得承认  罗曼  你是.. 你自封是
-I... I think you'd agree, Roman that you're a... self-admitted...
抱歉  我不知道用你的语言 该怎么说
Sorry, I don't know how you'd say this
但是... 是一个
in your language but a...
性变态
a sexual pervert.
你们真是...   -是吗
You're an... -Right?
有意思的一家人
-You're an interesting family.
有趣的家伙
Funny guy.
不说笑了
Well, all jokes aside
我听说  你近来一直
I heard that you may have been getting some tremors
被助理联系  这是真的吗
on the assistant loop, is this true?
是的
Yeah.
有人在斯莱克[企业聊天工具]上打给我
A call went out on LackeySlack
因为有很多狮树财务顾问和投资银行公司
because there are a number of advisors
的顾问 进城了  懂的都懂
in town from LionTree, apparently
他们不喜欢这种
and they don't like the feel
意大利硬枕的感觉
of the hard Italian pillows?
所以...但那是...那是私人谈话
So... but that's a... It's a private chat, so.
好了  闭嘴  谢谢
Yeah, shut up, All right. Thank you.
你好 抱歉   -你好
Hey, excuse me.
你刚刚跟格丽说了什么
What did you say to Gerri just now?
没什么
Nothing.
没什么?
Nothing?
你为什么要撒谎
And why are you lying?
是他让你撒谎的吗
Did he tell you to lie?
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
你是打算怀我老爸的孩子吗
Are you trying to have a baby with my dad?
那是个极其愚蠢的想法
Because that's an incredibly stupid idea.
哥  -他生下来就会很老
-Hey. -It'll be born old
得挂着拐杖
attached to a walker.
有一大群 新的并购顾问 来了奇安帝诺
So, there's a bunch of new M&A advisors in Chianciano.
我想 卡尔和弗兰克正在欧洲
And I think Karl and Frank are in Europe.
怎么回事 小罗 这是
What the fuck, Rome? What is...
我们被耍了吗
Are we being fucked?
卡尔
Karl?
欧洲的电话铃声
Euro ring.
喂  卡尔  你还好吗  你现在在哪  伙计
Hey, Karl, how you doing? Where are you, man?
在办公室  在你办公室
At the office? In your office?
很好  那你继续去忙你的公务吧
Great, well, I'll leave you to get on with your office job then
你这个混蛋
you motherfucker.
玛西娅那有什么消息吗   -没有
-Marcia? Anything? -No.
她一直在胡言乱语
Just throwing out bullshit.
你看到格丽了吗
Did you see Gerri?
之前那是怎么回事  -是啊
What the fuck? Before?  -Yeah.
这也太丑恶了  小罗
-This is ugly, Rome.
那么...   -什么
-So... -What?
我或许该说一句  有关那个会议的事
I should probably say, in terms of the meeting
马特森的确提出过一个想法
Matsson did float, as an idea
就是  他也许会收购我们
that maybe they'd buy us?
那爸怎么说的
And what did Dad say?
滚开
"fuck off!"
是吗  但他没回来吗
Mm-Hmm？ he stuck around?
是的  他没回来
He stuck around, yeah.
我的天呐
Jesus Christ.
你他妈为什么不早点告诉我   -是啊
Why the fuck didn't you tell me this earlier?
那个  肯
Hey.  Ken.
我们可能需要谈谈关于公司的事
We might need to talk. Company stuff.
我不...我不感兴趣  小西
I don't... I'm not interested, Shiv.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Yeah, sure.
但这他妈的 很重要 好吗
But this is fucking important, okay?
就五分钟  拜托了
Five minutes, please.
我们需要你联系一下 弗兰克 或是斯图伊
Just we need your line to Frank or Stewy maybe?
肯德尔  如果不是要紧事  我也不会来找你
Kendall, I wouldn't ask you if it wasn't important.
快点
Come on.
给老子跟上
Hurry the fuck up!
好吧  爸在背后阴我们
Okay. Well, Dad is doing us dirty, right?
你能别一下子就这么激动吗
Can you not make it a thing right away, okay?
事实上  我们不...  我们还不确定
We actually don't... We don't know yet.
马特森把他们要吞并我们的想法
Matsson pitched to Dad the idea
告诉了爸
of them eating us
但我想  他是在放风筝  开空头支票
but I think he was flying a kite,
爸  算是拒绝了
Dad kind of shut it down.
是吗  他 算是拒绝了吗
Okay. He kind of shut it down?
那为什么不久前  爸让他滚了呢
Because a moment ago, he told him to fuck off!
好吧  我没有数他具体
Well, okay. Well, I didn't keep track
说了多少句脏话  西沃恩  知道吗
of the exact number of expletives he used, Siobhan, okay?
我又不是脏话计数器
I'm not a fuckometer.
拉里·范西塔特 现在和马特森 在瑞士
Okay, well, look. Larry Vansitart is in Switzerland with Matsson
也就是说 他正在找投资
so he's looking for financing.
爸和卡尔 还有弗兰克 抱团了
Dad is huddled with Karl and Frank.
我们的市值倾倒了
Our market caps have tipped.
当地小镇被一群新顾问给包下了
The local town's been bought out by a new set of advisors.
事态有变
Something has flipped.
是啊  是啊  但
Yeah, yeah. But Dad would never sell, would he?
喂  混蛋  爸绝不会卖公司的  对吧
Hey, asshole, Dad would never sell, right?
我不知道   -他真的会吗
I don't know. I mean, would he?
他要是卖了的话  我们能拿到...我不知道
And if he did, would we get... I don't know...
我们会得到保障吗
would we get fucking protection?
你们能 别捎上我吗
Can you guys just do this without me?
好吗  我..我不想卷入其中
Yeah? I... I don't wanna get into it.
等等 肯  抱歉 肯
Wait a minute, Ken. I'm sorry, Ken.
你是有插一脚吗  你是不是和马特森谈过
Do you have an angle on this? Are you speaking with Matsson?
莱尔德打电话给我  是怎么回事
Laird has called me, so what's that?
该死
Shit...
肯  我们能谈谈吗
Ken? Can we talk?
小西  我不在这里
Shiv, I'm not here.
嘿  老兄
Hey, buddy.
喂  你还好吗
Hey. You okay?
我非常不对劲  小西
There's something really wrong with me, Shiv.
我不知道自己到底怎么了
I don't know what the fuck is wrong with me.
好吧  那..
Well...it's okay. It's...
我...我只是...
I'm just...
我觉得现在自己
I'm not feeling very connected
对孩子们
to my children
或是我的事业  都满不在意
or my endeavors right now.
我也无法 同时做好两件事 你知道吗
And...I can't get one thing right with another, you know?
我.我...
I'm...
我不知道怎么了  我试着去做什么
I don't know what happened, I tried to do something
我尽力了... 真的尽力了
I really... I tried.
我尽力了
I tried.
我知道  伙计
I know, man.
我知道  你搞砸了
I know, you fucked it.
去你的
fuck you.
就是这样
Well, that's what happened, yeah.
我尽力尝试了
I took a shot,
但  这就好像
but it's, like...
这不重要  但是...做生意就这样  好吗
-it didn't matter. But... -It's just business, okay?
就好像
Like...
我们都搞砸了  一切都...
we're all fucked.  Everything just sort of got...
搅和在一起
mixed up.
我以为我有出路了  我看得到...
I thought I had an out, I could see it, I could...
我能看到路标...
I could see the way markers
我以为我能
and I thought I could...
摆脱这一团乱麻  我以为我..
Out of all our shit, I thought I...
我以为我能带大家脱身  我...
I thought I could take us all out of it, I...
我确实... 尽力了
I did... I did try.
但是... 我不知道
But, I don't know.
我不是个好人
I'm not a good person.
无所谓了  你也还算好
Well, whatever, you're fine.
我...我很坏
I'm... I'm bad.
拜托
Come on.
放轻松点  忧郁男
Lighten up, glum-glum.
我杀了一个孩子
I killed a kid.
什么
What?
什么   -我杀了一个孩子
What? I killed a kid, and,
没错  他们...他们找上我了
yeah, they're...  They're coming for me.
他们会找上我的
They're gonna come for me.
这是...这是真的吗
Is this... Is this real?
什么鬼
What the fuck?
在你的婚礼上...什么
At your wedding. What?
胡说
Horse shit.
孩子
A kid.
那个孩子
That kid.
你是说那个...
You mean the
服务生吗  那个
waiter kid, the...
我当时嗑嗨了  然后在找
I was high and I was looking for...
找地方 再买点 我又喝醉了
To score and I was drunk
我神志不清地 醉驾了
I was fucked up, but I drove.
他看到了什么东西  他抢走了方向盘
And he saw something and he snatched at the wheel
然后我们坠河了
and we went into the water.
然后我丢下他跑了
And then I left him in there and ran.
好吧
Okay...
我们...我们得让你...来吧
Let's... We gotta get you... Come on. Let's...
我好憋屈
It's fucking lonely.
好了
Hey.
我快解体了
I'm all apart.
如果法庭认可的话
I mean, if it pleases the court
听起来  你并没有杀他
it sounds like you didn't kill him.
我觉得是他杀了他自己
It sounds to me like he killed him.
小罗  我就是一坨屎  兄弟
Roman, I'm a piece of shit, man.
但是
But...
是路和水 害死了他
the road and the water killed him?
听起来就是这样
That's what it sounds like.
不是  老弟  别安感我了
Nah, man. Don't.
不  我是认真的  我是说
No, seriously. I mean,
你撞车了以后呢  你逃逸了吗
you crashed, and then what? You did... You ran?
没 没有 我是说
No. No. I mean...
我试过救他
I tried to get him.
真的吗  那好  看到了吧
You did? Okay. See?
那..
That's...
我下潜过几次
I... I dived a few times.
对我而言  这听起来  就是个英雄故事
This sounds like the story of a hero to me
换成是我  肯定扭头就走
I would've been straight out of there.
说真的  我会像虎斑猫逃避洗澡一样
Serious, I would've been out of that water like a tabby cat
拔腿就跑
out of a bath.
别安慰我了
Don't, man.
别了
Don't.
别安慰我了  我是杀人区手
Don't, man, I'm a killer.
去你的
fuck you.
胡说  得了吧  你充其量不过是个.
Bullshit. Come on, at worst, you're...
是个不负责任的人  好吧
You're an irresponsibler, okay?
你太高估自己了
You're bigging yourself up.
好吧
Yeah?
我不知道
I don't know, you guys.
I don't know.
我干疮百孔了
I'm blown into a million pieces.
好了  我们得带你离开这里
Okay, we gotta get you out of here.
什么... 我们要去哪里
What... Where do we go?
把他带回教堂
Bring him back to the chapel,
关进告解室  这办法能行
stuff him in a confessional  that'll fix it.
该死
Oh, shit.
莱尔德回我电话了
fucking Laird's called me back.
是吗   -是的 等我一下
-Yeah? -Yeah. Just one minute.
是吗   -是啊
-Yeah? -Yeah.
好吧  接吧
Yeah. Okay. Take that call.
留我独自应付这位 "百感交集"的朋友  谢谢你
Leave me here with all the feelings, thank you.
喂  莱尔德  说吧  怎么了
Hey, Laird. Siobhan, what's up?
谁没开着保时捷
I mean, who hasn't clipped the odd kid with the Porsche
撞死过小孩呢  对吧
am I right?
仿佛成人礼一样
Yeah, I mean, it's like a rite of passage.
我也杀过一个孩子  有什么大不了的
I've killed a kid too, big deal.
小西
Shiv.
你杀过一个孩子对吧   -对
You've killed a kid, right?  Yeah.
老哥  你花样百出地 搞糟了我的婚礼
Man, you fucked my wedding in so many ways.
对不起
I'm sorry.
少了一个服务员  这就说得通了
You know, one waiter down, that makes sense.
我等了好长时间  才在她的婚礼上  喝上一杯
It took me forever to get a fucking drink at her wedding.
别这样  老弟   -好吧
-Please, man. -Okay, yeah.
我不能.
I can't do this.
你说得对  我是个
You're right. I'm a...
我只是想说
I guess I'm just trying to say like...
谁才是真正的受害者
who's the real victim here?
我等了三刻钟  才喝上一杯金汤力
I waited three quarters of an hour for a gin and tonic.
好的
Okay.
好了
抱歉...
Sorry to
我想说... 肯... 已经确认了
say this, Ken, but confirmed.
莱尔德是交易中的一员
Laird is inside the deal
但他已经被剥夺了主导权
but he's been cucked out of the lead,
所以 他满腹牢骚
so he's bitter and bleeding.
Gojo 收购韦斯达
GoJo buys Waystar.
他们出了高价  爸把现金和股票
They pay a premium, Dad cashes out, cash and stock
都套现了  可能还留了一个头衔
cash and stock and he keeps maybe a title.
但是
But...
拿走一些资产
And takes a few assets
但董事会已经是马特森的了
but it's Matsson's fucking board.
消息可信吗  是真的吗
That's... Can we trust that? Is that real?
肯德尔  我知道现在不太合适
Kendall, I know this isn't ideal
但我们必须讨论一下
but we have to talk about this now.
听着 我来叫车  我们赶紧离开这鬼地方
Look, I've called a car, let's just get the fuck out of here.
你想在哪儿等
Where do you wanna wait?
我可以...我可以和你们在一起吗
Can I be with you guys?
当然  可以  -好的
-Yeah. Of course. -Okay.
好了  所以..
Okay, so
我们得阻止这一切
we gotta go stop this.
什么鬼
-What the fuck?
是的
-Yeah.
我们去找他  告诉他  我们不接受  好吗
So, we go see him and we tell him we just won't have it, right?
小罗
Rome.
好吧
Okay.
这只是谣言
This is rumors.
所以  我要直接和他单独谈
So I will need to talk him directly, just me.
你觉得  你和他很亲近吗
Do you think you're close to him?
你只是他的狗腿子
You're just his little rat fucker.
我只是说  事实上
I'm just saying, as a matter of fact
爸和我近期一直合作密切
that Dad and I have been working closely lately
我不想太咄咄逼人
and I don't wanna go in too aggressive.
我不会冲进去喊“小西战队万岁“的  好吗
I'm not busting in there crying "Team Shiv", okay?
我们还不知道局势会如何发展
We don't know how this is gonna play out just yet.
你觉得爸在保护你吗
You think Dad is protecting you?
不行  让马特森掌权  爸就是断了我们的后路
No, we let Matsson take control, that is Dad slamming the door.
说明 他从不认为 我们将会
It means that he doesn't ever think that we will, can
可以或者应该 接管公司
or should take over.
我只是觉得  我们不该这么咄咄逼人
I just don't think we should be aggressive.
我们真的能阻止他吗
I mean, can we even actually stop him?
能
Yes.
控制权的变更
A change of control
需要取得控股公司绝对多数股东的同意
needs a super majority in the holding company.
妈离婚时给了我们权利  他需要取得我们的同意
Mom got us that in the divorce so they need us on board.
好吧  但是
Right. Well,
我不确定我想用这种方法
I'm not sure I wanna pull out a move like that.
也许  我只想安于现状
Maybe I just stick with what I got.
什么现状
Which is what?
存满屌照的硬盘吗   -说得妙啊
Hard drive full of dick pics? Nice.
就是...
Which is...
我想在爸爸的幕后操纵下
I think with Dad pulling the strings...
你觉得  我们在马特森的新组织架构中  会处于什么位置  小罗
Where do you think we fit on Matsson's new org chart, Rome?
他会逼你退位  把你关入地下室  仅此而已
He'll Romanov you and take you to the cellar and that's that.
小罗 你知道  爸永远不会选你
Rome, you know Dad is never gonna choose you
是因为他觉得  你有毛病
because he thinks there's something wrong with you.
抱歉  但是...
I'm sorry, but maybe it's time
也许我们该对彼此坦白了
that we said these things to each other
而不是对“名利场"大吐苦水
instead of just talking it all out to Vanity Fair.
那这个控股公司的方法
And the holding company move.
如果我们这样做了  会有效吗
If we do that, that's real?
没有我们的同意  他无法批准交易
He can't sanction a deal without us,
这是法律事实
that's a legal fact.
阻止他  他就完了
Block him and he's fucked.
好吧  所以
Okay, so,
是时候撕破脸了
time to rip off the Band-Aid.
我们...我们把他逐出公司
We just push him out.
让他孤立无援  然后我们点出他有泌尿疾病
We get him on his own and we say urinary tract
再拉拢董事会
-we say shareholder meeting.
是的  他在乔希家差点死了
-Right  he nearly fucking croaked at Josh's.
是的  他疯了  他在操一个20 多岁的人
Yeah, he's out of it. He's fucking a 20-year-old
还打算要个试管婴儿
and he's planning for babies in jars.
他已经失去理智了  而且他...他还想卖掉公司
You know, he's gone loopy and he's tried to sell the shop.
所以  即便只是 操他助理这件事
So, I mean, even just fucking his assistant
我们告诉董事会的话  他就完蛋了
we tell the board that, he's toast.
我们把他逐出去
We push him out.
发动政变
Full coup.
对  逼他出局
Yeah. Slide him out.
怎么说  肯当董事长
Say, Ken, chair...
小罗  你或者我当首席执行官
you, or me, Rome, CEO
还有个兄弟 就担任
and the other one takes
随便他们想要什么业务  比如录音棚电影电视.
whatever they want like studio, movies, TV,
直播之类的  但是你懂的  是平等分配
the streamer, but, you know, equal.
好吧  但得是真正的平等分配
Okay, but really equal,
真的平等  如果我们要这么做
really equal. If we do this
我不希望 你们两个家伙 摆出大哥哥大姐姐的架势
I don't want you two cunts trying to big brother me out
吞掉本属于我的那份  好吗
of my fucking piece, okay?
不会的  我们可以争出个分配方案  这..会很有趣的
No, we can fight it out. It'll... It'll be fun.
确实会很有意思
That will be fun.
我们用商务车把墨索里尼[洛根]送到医院
We fucking take Mussolini away in a van to the hospital
接手广播电台业务
and take over the radio stations.
妈的
Oh, fuck.
我确实觉得
I do think that
尽管说这话 我自己都想吐
even though this literally makes me wanna vomit
因为 我每天都想 干掉你俩
and I wanna kill you both every day
而且 一切必会槽糕地收场
and it's all gonna end horribly
但 我确实相信 我们...
I do think that we...
爷吐了
puke,
我们可能会成为一支很棒的队伍
could make a pretty good team.
所以  我们是怎么看待干掉老爸的
So, how do we feel about killing Dad?
百感交集吗
Mixed feelings?
把机关枪递给我   -好的
Pass me the fucking shotgun.  Okay.
小罗  加入我们吗
Rome, you in?
可以  去他妈的  可以
Okay. fuck. Okay.
老康  是我  给你更新下近况
Well, Con, this is me layering you in.
但  现在我没空细说
But I can't talk about this right now
因为这件事很复杂  我没空
because it's complicated and I don't have time.
而且  你还有点反应迟钝
-And also you're a little bit slow.
对  谢谢你接我的电话
-Hey, yeah, thanks for talking.
我就是想要再三确认  控股公司的章程
I just wanna triple check the holding company by-law shit.
我们有武器  公司控制权转移的否决权
We have a weapon. Veto on a change of control.
是爸妈离婚协议里的  所以  一旦我们否决了公司控制权转移
It's from the divorce, so stop that
交易就会瓦解  他就无能为力了
and the deal collapses, he's impotent.
我们会逼他出局的
We're gonna force him out.
靠  好的
fuck, okay.
小西  那我会在什么位置呢
But where do I fit in, Shiv?
这个嘛  汤姆 高层吧  我也不清楚...  这...
Well, high up, Tom, I don't know. It...
但我们会想出来的  现在有太多事要处理了
We'll figure it out though. There's a lot going on.
没事  当然  好的
No, sure, sure, okay.
但.. 高层吗
But... high?
但是  汤姆  一旦我们这么做了
But, Tom, once we do it right away
立马我们会让他打出医学牌
we're gonna offer him the medical card
确保帝国的防卫[公司的安全]
secure the imperial guard.
告诉他  他需要休息
Tell him that he needs to take some rest
这个说法的来源  就是我们这些孩子
and sourced to us kids,
我们会让泛美网科确认的
we'll get ATN to confirm.
比如说“创始人洛根·罗伊身体抱恙”
Say like, "Founder Logan Roy ailing"
为他祷告
"Prayers for the big man",
正在考虑退居二线
"Thinking of taking a step back".
所以  我们可以引用你  作为消息来源吗
So we can cite you as sources, yeah?
可以吗   -可以  我们会支持这个说法的
Yeah. And we'll stand it up.
准备好  好吗
Get ready, okay?
天啊  好的
Jesus. Okay.
好运
Good luck.
再见
Bye.
他加入了吗   -对
He's in?  Yeah.
你好啊  汤米
Hey, Tommy.
你好  -好啊
-Hey. -Hey.
你好
-Hey.
请向某人致意
Say hello to someone
这个人可能会成为
who could be Logan's ex-wife's
洛根前妻的 继表妹夫
step-cousin-in-law and heir apparent
卢森堡的继承人
to the Grand Duchy of Luxembourg.
从名单上 除名了十二次 或者别的
Twelve times removed or some shit.
还可能成为 某个地方的伯爵
And potential count of somewhere
意大利王位 潜在的合法继承人
and legitimate claimant to the Dormant throne of Italy.
格雷格  你在说什么
What, Greg?
我和女伯爵
Me and the Contessa.
我们之间来电了
We're hitting it off.
她觉得自己的个人品牌形象 面临着危机
She's having an existential crisis about her personal branding
而我可以用甜言蜜语 缓解她的焦虑
and I'm right in there to wheedle away.
那
What about...
康福莉吗   -对
-Comfry? -Yeah.
康福莉可能会帮她重新塑造个人品牌形象
Comfry might be helping her refresh her personal branding.
我.. 其实我觉得  她没有多喜欢我
And I don't actually think she's that into me.
我们正在分床睡「关系疏远]
We're separate bedding.
这是不含愧疚的转变
It's a guilt-free switch-up.
结案了
Case closed.
门砰的关上了
Slammed it shut.
法官大人判决结果是爱情
The verdict is love, Your Honor.
格雷格  听我说
Greg, listen.
出什么事了
What's up?
所以
So...
事情可能发生了一些变化
things may be in motion.
关于...
As in...
是有人要去坐牢了吗   -不是
-Is anyone going to jail? -No.
不是的  所以..
No. So...
你想和我一起吗
do you wanna come with me?
斯普鲁斯
Sporus?
我能知道更多信息吗
Can I ask for a little more information?
不能
No.
应该不能
I don't think so.
我也许需要你当我的护卫犬
I might need you as my attack dog.
好的   -比如 格雷格威尔士梗
-Right. -Like a Greg-weiler.
汤姆的护卫犬
Tom's attack dog.
真棒
Nice.
我的意思是
I mean...
我的口袋里揣着 明亮星游轮的 水牛城业务
I have Brightstar Buffalo in my hip pocket.
我还算是个有头有脸的人物  所以...
I'm kind of a big deal, so...
格雷格  你在国会面前搞砸了
You fucked yourself before congress, Greg.
那.. 那只是你的看法
That's your opinion.
法官大人  我不记得了.
"But I don't recall, Your Honor. I don't recall..."
兄弟  你他妈就是个笑话
You're a fucking joke, man.
是谁一直在这个大家族里照顾你
Who has ever looked after you in this fucking family, huh?
好吧  关于..
All right, well, in terms
我能到什么位置
of where I could be getting to,
如果我跟你一起的话
if I were to come with.
你可以从永无止境的中层
You could be heading away from the endless middle
前进到高层的一席
and towards the bottom of the top.
高层的一席?
The bottom of the top?
我能有我自己的..
Could I get my own...
我自己的  比如..
-My own, like...
你自己的格雷格吗  对
-Your own Greg?  -Yeah.
你可以有20个格雷格
-You can have 20.
听我说  我...我还有点事要处理
Listen, I have things to do.
你想和魔鬼交易吗
Do you want a deal with the devil?
这个嘛..
Well...
灵魂对我来说有什么用吗
what am I gonna do with a soul anyways?
灵魂太无聊了
Souls are boring.
去你的  灵魂
Boo, souls.
当然愿意
Of course.
好  -好
-Okay. -Okay.
好的   -好的
-All right. -All right.
也许他在打盹
Maybe he's napping.
行吧  不好意思要吵醒他了
Yeah. Then worst to wake him up.
我们之间挺好的吧   -挺好的
-We're good? -Yeah, yeah.
我挺好的  罗曼  你还好吗
I'm good. You good, Rome?
我挺好的
Yeah.
你能搞定这个吗
You can handle this?
基本上  从四岁起  就在计划这一天的到来了
Been basically planning it since we were four.
罗曼  要是老爸含情脉脉望向你  怎么办
What if Dad flutters his eyelids at you, Rome?
你会融化吗
-You gonna melt?
我吗  不会
-Me? No.
只要你们不在巴厘岛打水枪
As long as you guys don't go water pistols in Bali.
巴厘岛打水枪?
Water pistols in Bali?
对  在巴厘岛打水枪
Yeah, water pistols in Bali
那次我们打算一起用水枪偷袭老爸
when we were all gonna go squirt Dad under the canopy?
我上了  你们就他妈的把我一个人留在那里
I went in and you fucks left me for dead?
我不记得了
I don't recall.
真省事
That's convenient.
嘿  老爸
Hey, Dad.
我是小西·罗伊  我们进去了
Shiv Roy. We're going in.
好的  抱歉 律师先生  我能看看吗
Okay, yeah. Excuse me, lawyery man, may I see that?
不行
-No.
好吧  我爸在哪里  洛根  洛根·罗伊
-Okay. Where's my dad? Logan, Logan Roy?
我不知道我还没看见他
-I don't know, I haven't seen him.
你还没看见他  真省事
-Oh, you haven't seen him.  That's convenient.
他还没看见他
He hasn't seen him.
兄弟们
Guys.
看看是谁
Well, look who it is.
那什么  我们要进去
Hey, we're going in.
让他们进来
Send them in!
好吧
Okay
你好啊  -你们好啊
-Hey. -Hey!
大家好
Hello, hello.
这是在干嘛   -各位好
What's all this now? Hi, hi everyone, hi.
你好 卡尔   -你好
-Hey, Karl. -Hi.
老爸  我们就是有点局外人的感觉
We're just feeling a little out of the loop, Dad.
当然了  事情的变化很快
Oh, of course, things have moved very fast.
进来吧  都进来
Come in...
我们可能搞错了
Yeah, we might be wrong,
但我们
but we're
听到有关 GoJo 的传言
hearing rumors about GoJo?
没错  听说
Yeah, that
我们可能会成为收购目标
we might be the target now.
是这样吗  爸
Is that right, Dad?
好吧  我在考虑一些选择
Okay. I've been looking at some options.
那好  我们的职位可能受到影响
Right. We might be affected, our positions
所以我们想澄清形势
so we wanted to get some clarity.
当然可以  但你们介意把这位请出去吗
Absolutely. But do you mind not with him in here
他一直在给我眼神杀
giving me the fucking doggy-evils?
罗慕路斯 你能带他出去吗
Can you take him out, Romulus?
我会给你妹妹介绍情况 给你提些观点
I'll fill in your sister and give you the angles.
我不信任他
I don't trust him.
罗曼
Roman.
你可以告诉我们  爸
You can tell us together, Dad.
我以为咱们已经说清楚了
I thought we had this figured out.
是的  只是如果  我们都听一听的话
Yeah. It just might be better, you know,
可能会更好
if we all hear.
好
Okay.
情况就是  我们公司的市值
So the market capitalizations of our firm
有所变动
is a bit on the move.
生意每况愈下
Ours is a declining business.
所以  在我看来  正在发生的合并浪潮
There's a wave of consolidations happening
意味着  现在是与严肃的科技公司
that mean this is the optimal moment, in my opinion
也就是 GoJo 进行交易的
to make a deal with a serious tech operation
最佳时机
like GoJo.
这就是我在着手的东西  行了吗
And that's what I've been exploring, okay?
好的  那么  代表我们全体的意见  我想说
Okay, so, I would say on behalf of all of us
你能否放慢速度  放我们进来
can you ease up and let us in
停止收购进程  直到我们看清  到底受到什么样的撞击
stop this until we see exactly how we're impacted?
不行  必须是现在
-No, it has to be now.
为什么   -因为我有预感
-Why?  Because I feel it in my bones.
哦 哇哦 没法反驳这一点呢
Oh, wow, no arguing with that, huh?
到头来  这就是我的法宝
End of the day, that's all I fucking got.
你知道自己在胡说八道吧
Well, you know that's bullshit.
听着  这是出售的最佳时机
Look, this is the best moment to sell.
如果 我做不到 随时随地敲定 最好的交易
If I don't do the best deal at any given point
一切又有什么意义
what's the point of anything?
如果我不退出 意味着 放着50亿美元不要
I don't get out, I leave five billion on the table.
拜托  爸
Come on, Dad,
你要50亿干什么呢
what are you gonna do with the five bil?
把它 跟你其他的钱 堆在一起吗
Put it on your pile with all your other fucking bill?
可能是吧  没错
Probably. Yeah.
那我们该怎么办
And what are we supposed to do?
堆你们自己的钱啊
Make your own fucking pile.
我知道 这是一次巨大的调整
I know this is a readjustment
但我们在流血  别人嗅得到  我需要快速行动
but our blood's in the water and I need to make moves fast
才能掌握局面  让我自己
in order to control the situation and get myself
和你们...
and you
未来得到保障
assurances for the future.
爸  一旦马特森发号施令  我们就完了
Dad, once Matsson is calling the shots, we're fucked.
不会的  他很看好你
No, nah, he rates you.
这对你们来说  也是一次
And this is an opportunity for you kids
学习的机会...
to get
学会怎么应对现实
an education in real life.
有你在上面  我们能接管公司
With you at the top, we can take over
但没了你  我们就完了
but without you, we're fucked.
走吧  罗曼
Come on, Roman.
离这些 雅各宾派 远点
Let's get away from these fucking Jacobins.
你有我呢  来吧  我们谈谈
I've got you, come on, let's discuss.
爸  我...我知道他说了什么
Okay, Dad, I know what he said,
我也在场  但是
I was there, but...
真的  如果马特森发号施令
really, with Matsson calling the shots
我们...就会被吊在城门示众了
we're strung up in the town square.
怎么会
No,
他很看好你
he rates you.
我向你保证
You have my word.
这是一次机会  儿子
This is an opportunity, son.
需要一点勇气
A bit of fucking grit.
面对逆境  就像我
Adversity, like me.
你可以相信我
You can trust me.
你不能相信他
You can't trust him.
我们在这里告诉你  我们仨一起
We're here to say, the three of us
请求你
to ask and to say
不要这样做  求你了
do not do this, please.
如果我决定不听从你们的呢
And what if I decide I can't listen to you?
我们可以阻止你
We can stop you
我们会阻止你的  搞砸交易
and we will stop you.  Blow this up.
你要变更控制权  需要我们的同意
You need our vote for a change of control.
对  你需要我们所有人的同意
Yeah. You need all of us.
你需要超级多数  我们可以不给你
You need a super majority and we can kill it
也不会给你
and we will.
你们他妈的 玩过家家呢
You're playing toy fucking soldiers!
去啊
Go on,
滚啊
fuck off!
我打败你们了
I have you beat!
你们几个蠢货
You morons!
不会的  因为你需要超级多数
Well, no, because you need a super majority
不会的
Oh well no
因为你需要超级多数...
because you need to have a super majority to...
她还在吗
Is she still on?
全都搞定了
It's all done.
我们能拨回去吗
Can we get her back on?
爸  什么情况
Dad, what is this?
好
Yeah.
喂  我在 洛根
Hello, yeah. Logan?
卡洛琳  我开免提了
Caroline, you're on
罗曼  肯德尔  西沃恩都在
with Roman, Kendall, and Siobhan.
喂   妈  -妈
-Hi, Mom. -Mom?
好吧  我今晚不想再
All right, well, I don't necessarily wanna do
帮你做什么了  洛根
anymore tonight, Logan.
我和你妈 在审核 之前离婚协议的
Your mother and I have been reviewing the terms of the
条款
divorce agreement.
妈  你搞死我们了
-Mom, you fucked us.
我们同意
-And we've agreed
之前的安排有一点
that the arrangements were a little
过时了 -操 啊 妈  他拿下你了
antiquated.   Oh, fuck, Mom, he got to you.
真的吗  妈  这么快
Oh, seriously, Mom, already?
你他妈到底   -听着
-What the fuck did you... -Look,
我没法深入谈论  好吗..
I can't get into it  all right?
我觉得一切都会好的
I... I think everything will be fine.
雷克斯·亨顿在处理事宜
Rex Hendon's dealing with it all.
妈  你把孩子们全杀了
Mom, you just slit our throats.
请不要生气  我...
Please, don't be angry. I...
我觉得 这是最好的结局
I think this is for the best.
彼得很期待
Peter's so excited.
是吗  彼得很期待  太好了
Oh, is he? Peter's excited, great.
我不确定 这些对你们 有什么好处
I'm not sure it's been good for you all
抱歉了  不好意思
but, you know, I'm sorry.
我爱你们  挂了
I love you all. Bye.
我们走进了爸妈的圈套
Oh, we just walked in on Mom and Dad fucking us.
谢谢你  卡洛琳
Thank you, Caroline.
爸.
Dad...
求你了   -求你了
-please? -Please?
求你了
Please.
我会助那个势力狂一臂之力
The seat sniffer gets a fucking leg up.
这是交易
That's a deal.
你手里有什么值得交易的筹码
What have you got in your fucking hand?
我手里有什么
What have I got?
我不知道...
I don't know,
爱算吗
fucking love?
爱
Love?
你来讨伐我
You come for me
是带着爱的吗
with love.
你冲进门来  全副武装
You bust in here, guns in hand
随后发现  手里的枪  都变成了香肠
and now you find they've turned to fucking sausages.
现在你给我谈爱了
You talk about love?
你本该相信我的
You should have trusted me.
爸  为什么 为什么
Dad, why? Why?
因为这行得通
Because it works.
我他妈赢了
I fucking win.
去吧 去吧 滚
Oh, go on, go on. fuck off.
爱管闲事的路人
You nosy fucking pedestrians.
-爸  -喂
-Dad. -Hey.
罗伊先生  罗伊先生  稍等
Mr. Roy, hold on a second.
我需要你签  -谁告诉他的
I need you to sign... Who the fuck told him?
谁告诉他 我们要来的
Who told him that we were coming?
格丽 格丽 格丽
Gerri...Gerri...Gerri...
他不对劲
he's not well.
你能帮助我们的  对吧  你能帮我们阻止他的
You can help us, right? You can help us stop him?
我更在乎
Well, I'm focused on
任何 最符合 公司股东
whatever outcome best serves the financial interest
经济利益 的结果
of the shareholders of the company.
这不符合我的利益
But it doesn't serve my interests.
这怎么会符合我的利益呢
How does it serve my interests?
等会   -好的
Later. Okay
小西
Hey, Shiv.
你还好吗
You okay?
你好  -你好
-Hey. -Hey.
还好
Yeah.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
出什么事了    -妈搞死我们了
What's going on? Mom fucked us.
什么
What?
没事了
Hey.